Morris, James O., Office Files /4073
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILR 200B - Course Outline - Fall 1969 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1969 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- ILR 200 - Reserve List, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 58)
- ILR 200B - Fall 1970 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- ILR 200F - Fall 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- ILR 250 - Summer 1971, 1959-1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- ILR 286 - Spring Term 1973, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Summary of Activities - Fall 1956, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- ILR 293 - Course, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- ILR 293 - Summer 1957 - Final Exam (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Mid-term Exam - ILR 293 - Summer 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- ILR 306 - Fall 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- ILR 306 - Fall 1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- ILR 306 - Spring 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- ILR 307, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- ILR 485 - Fall Term 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1978, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1980 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- ILR 307 - Spring 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- ILR 307 - Fall 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- ILR 307 - Bibliography, 1973-1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Supplemental Book Bibliographies, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- ILR 350 - Labor History - Fall 1957 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- ILR 352 - Mid-term - July 23, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- ILR 380 - Spring 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- ILR 380 - Spring 1978, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- ILR 380 - Spring 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- ILR 405 - Exam File, 1978-1983 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1982 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- ILR 702 - Fall 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- ILR 702 - Spring 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- A - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Includes news clippings; includes some Spanish language material
- B - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Includes news clippings; includes some Spanish language material; includes postcards
- Dean Catherwood - Correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- C - Correspondence, 1953-1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- D - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- E - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- F - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes postcards
- Ford Foundation, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Fulbright and Latour, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Fulbright Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- G - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- H - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- I - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- ILR Staff memorandums, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- J - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes a street map of a neighborhood in Mexico City
- K - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- L - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Professor Henry Landsberger, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Mc - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Dean John W. McConnell, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- M - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- N - Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  Includes postcards
- N - Mr. Bernard G. Naas, 1955-1961 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- O - Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- P - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Pan American Union, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  Entirely Spanish language material
- R - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Professor Risley Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- S - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  Includes postcards; includes some Spanish language material
- Doris Stevenson Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- T - Correspondence, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- U - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- V - Correspondence, 1954-1964 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  Includes a street map of a neighborhood in Mexico City; includes some Spanish language material
- W - Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- XYZ - Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Brookwood Study - Correspondence regarding personal interviews (New York and Washington D.C.), 1956 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Green Copy Letters - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Latin American Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Guatemala Seminar, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Honduras Seminar, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- El Salvador Seminar, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- A - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Cornell University - Business Leadership Course for American Airlines Program Summary, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- B - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Jean Boivin - Graduate Student, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- C - Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- D - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- E - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- F - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Faculty Legislation, 1954-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- G - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Graduate Committee, 1956-1968 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- H - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- I - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- J - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- K - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- L - Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- M - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Mc - Correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- N - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- O - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Planning Committee, 1955-1973 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Acting Dean Robert F. Risley, 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- P - Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- R - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- S - Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- T - Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- U - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- V - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- W - Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- XYZ - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- AFL, Cannon, and Republican Progressives, 1913-1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Busbey on Cannon, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Excerpts from Busbey's Uncle Joe Cannon
- Bolles on Cannon, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Excerpt from Bolles's Tyrant from Illinois
- Gwinn on Cannon, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Excerpts from Gwinn's Uncle Joe Cannon: Archfoe of Insurgency
- Cannon 1906, 1903-1906 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 1906 General (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Cannon 1907, 1907-1908 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Cannon February 20, 1908 - August 30, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Cannon September 6, 1908 - September 22, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Cannon September 24 to end of 1908 - campaign, 1908-1909 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Cannon 1909 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Cannon 1910, 1909-1910 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- P. J. McGuire on Debs 1897 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Theodore Roosevelt and Labor, 1904 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Littlefield Campaign 1906 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- 1907 General (Box 23, Folder 16)
- 1908 General (February - April), 1908-1915 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- 1908 General (May - September 15), 1908-1912 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- 1908 General (September 15 - December) (Box 23, Folder 19)
- 1909 General (Box 23, Folder 20)
- 1910 General (Box 23, Folder 21)
- 1912 General, 1912-1916 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- 1914 General (Box 23, Folder 23)
- 1916 General, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Gompers-McDonald 1914, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- 1915 - End of Protocol, Williams papers) (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Borah Land Fraud, 1906-1976 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- The Howell-Barkley Bill (Box 23, Folder 28)
- The Genesis of the Railway Labor Act - Politics, Power, and Progressivism in the 1920s (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Howell-Barkley Round Two (Box 23, Folder 30)
- General Atterbury Takes Command (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Victory at Last (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Mitchell - Last Rough Draft (Box 24, Folder 1)
- The Acquisitive Spirit of John Mitchell, UMW President (1899-1908), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Drafts of The Acquisitive Spirit of John Mitchell (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Drafts of The Acquisitive Spirit of John Mitchell continued (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Notes on John Mitchell (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Handwritten Pages of the Mitchell Article (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Mitchell Manuscript and Request for Comments, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Mitchell Manuscript and Request for Comments continued, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- James O. Morris Analysis of Mitchell's Income and Investments (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Mitchell Revision File, 1909-1912 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Bibliography, 1890-1962 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Index of Folder Contents (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Unclassified, 1901-1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Background and UMW Salary, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- M's Character, 1908 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Powder, 1903-1908 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Coal Consolidation, 1901-1903 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Chanute Oil, 1904-1906 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Bolen-Darnall Oil, 1904 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Coal Lands - Barnaby, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Stocks - Charles Gates and Company, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Stocks - Peabody and Harris Winthrop, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Stocks - Peabody and Harris Winthrop continued, 1902-1908 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Stocks - Easely and Keefe, 1907 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Knee Hole Coal Company, 1905-1907 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- John G. Taylor - Insurance, 1900-1904 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- John G. Taylor - Soap, 1902-1903 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Louisiana Land, 1904-1908 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Dernell 1900, 1901-1907 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Lovell and Buffington, 1903-1908 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Pictures and Pens, etc., 1900-1901 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  Letters relating to the selling of pictures and pens of John Mitchell
- Shoes, 1902-1909 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Passes, 1899-1907 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Gifts from Miners, 1900-1903 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Writings - Book, 1903-1907 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Writings - Miscellaneous and Lectures, 1901-1907 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Writings - Ridsdale, 1904-1905 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Writings - Boyce's Weekly, 1902-1903 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- National Civic Federation (NCF) - Easely, 1901-1907 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Carbonium Company, 1899-1902 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Alabama Property, 1901 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Spring Valley Property, 1901-1908 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Stock - American Fraternal Life, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Edward F. Blewitt, 1901-1908 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Hammerling, 1902-1908 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- W. R. Russell - Coal and Oil, 1902-1907 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Summary - Income and Investments, 1898-1908 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Retirement - Job Offers, 1899-1908 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Retirement - Job Offers Alcoholism, 1900-1908 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Clubs, 1900-1909 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Savings, 1905-1908 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Loans, 1902-1908 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Coal and Coke Company - Frank Strong, 1902 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- International Correspondent School, 1905-1906 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Hanna, 1900-1903 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Criticism of Mitchell, 1901-1906 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Payoff - Dolan, 1906-1907 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Stocks, 1908-1909 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Misuse of Union Funds, 1899-1908 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Banking - McHenry, 1905-1908 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Conclusion, 1902-1908 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Unclassified, 1898-1901 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Southwestern Strike, 1899-1900 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Teamsters and Peabody, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Missouri 1901 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Colorado Trip, 1902 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Bitum 1902 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Bitum 1903 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Bitum 1904 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Herrin Explosion 1904 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Powder, 1901-1904 (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Colorado, Victor Fuel 1904 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Negotiations Bitum 1905 (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Negotiations Bitum 1906 (Box 25, Folder 65)
- Bitum 1907 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Bitum 1908 (Box 25, Folder 67)
- Negotiations Anthracite, 1900-1905 (Box 25, Folder 68)
- Negotiations Steel 1901 (Box 25, Folder 69)
- Notes on the Mitchell Papers (Box 25, Folder 70)
- ILR 100 - History of Industrial Relations - Fall 1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- ILR 405 - Dramatic Events - Summer 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- ILR 380 - Famous Trials in American Labor History - Spring 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- ILR 101 - History of American Labor and Politics - Spring 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- ILR 307 - Biographies - Fall 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- ILR 100 - History of Industrial Relations - Fall 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- ILR 405 - Summer 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- ILR 405 - Summer Session 1980, 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- J. O. Morris, 1974-1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Draft Manuscript - The Plumb Plan (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Footnotes and Bibliography (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Draft Manuscript - Chiefs Put in the Thumb, Abandon Plumb (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Draft Manuscript - The Howell-Barkley Bill: Round One (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Draft Manuscript - Howell-Barkley: Round Two (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Draft Manuscript - General Atterbury Takes Command (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Draft Manuscript - Victory at Last (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Untitled Manuscript Pages (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Film Orders for ILR 405 - Summer 1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- The Genesis of the Railway Labor Act - Politics, Power, and Progressivism in the 1920s (Box 26, Folder 20)
- The Genesis of the Railway Labor Act continued (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Philip Foner and the Writing of The Joe Hill Case, 1965-1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Unsorted Note Cards and Bibliography (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Box of Note Cards - ILR 307 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Box of Note Cards - J. O. Morris - ILR 480 - Famous Trials (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Box of Note Cards - Bibliography - ILR 100 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Did LaFollette Expect to Win? (Box 27, Folder 64)
- General Assessment of Party Campaign and Voter Turnout (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Bornet (Box 27, Folder 58)
- LaFollette Campaign of 1924 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- RP Convention June 1924 (Box 27, Folder 60)
- McAdoo 1924 Primary in Ohio (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Shaver: 1924 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Analysis of 1924 Campaign (Box 27, Folder 63)
- LaFollette and RP + DP - 1924 Conventions, July 4 Meeting CPPA, and LaF's Campaign (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Analysis of Vote for LaFollette (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Daugherty's Resignation and Wheeler (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Daugherty's Resignation + Wheeler (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Teapot Dome (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Progressive Legislation in 1920's (Box 27, Folder 69)
- DP Convention 1924 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Republican Progressives and 1924 Campaign (Box 27, Folder 62)
- Journal BLF + E May-Aug 1924 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- AFL - 1923 (May 21-Aug 10) (Box 27, Folder 40)
- AFL 1923 (Aug 13-Dec 31) (Box 27, Folder 41)
- AFL Proceedings, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Am Fed (Jan-Sept 1924) (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Am Fed (Sept-Dec 1924) (Box 27, Folder 44)
- White (Box 27, Folder 57)
- Journal BLF + E Sept-Dec 1924 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Farm Vote 1920's, 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Journal Conductor 1924 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Journal M of Way 1924 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- BLE Journal Jan-July 1924 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- 1924 Election (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Harding and Labor (Box 27, Folder 103)
- LaFollette and the Farmer - Labor Party Convention June 17, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Journal BLF + E Jan-May 1924 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Daves (Box 27, Folder 96)
- BLE Journal July-Dec 1924 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- Beveridge (Box 27, Folder 90)
- Borah (Box 27, Folder 91)
- Sen. Borah (Box 27, Folder 92)
- Edward T. Clark (Coolidge Sec.) (Box 27, Folder 93)
- Election of 1924 - General (Box 27, Folder 88)
- Couzens (Box 27, Folder 95)
- Coolidge on Labor (Box 27, Folder 87)
- Harding's Sec. of Labor - James J. Davis (Box 27, Folder 97)
- Sec. of Labor James J. Davis (Box 27, Folder 98)
- Harding - General (Box 27, Folder 99)
- Harding (Box 27, Folder 100)
- Assessment of Harding (Box 27, Folder 101)
- Harding + Labor (Box 27, Folder 102)
- General Assessment of Coolidge Admin (Box 27, Folder 94)
- Analysis of LaF. Vote 1924 (Box 27, Folder 81)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (and N-P League) (Box 27, Folder 73)
- 1924 Election Results and Collapse of CPPA (Box 27, Folder 74)
- LaFollette-Wheeler Campaign Sept-Nov 1924 (Box 27, Folder 75)
- LaFollette + CPPA June-Sept 1924 (Box 27, Folder 76)
- AFL and Internat. Policy, Early 1920's, 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 77)
- Norris - 1902 Campaign and Election (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Murray, 103rd Ballot (Box 27, Folder 89)
- RP Convention 1924 (Box 27, Folder 80)
- Plight of Farmers 1920's, 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Bryan Acceptance Speech (Box 27, Folder 82)
- Davis Acceptance Speech (Box 27, Folder 83)
- DP Platform 1924 (Box 27, Folder 84)
- Business and TLC American Plan 1920's, 1920-1929 (Box 27, Folder 85)
- Teapot and Dome and 1924 Election (Box 27, Folder 86)
- RP in 1924 before Convention (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Rehmus - Collective Bargaining and Technological Change on American Railroads, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Government Regulation of Railroad Labor Relations since 1920 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Bibliography - American Labor and Politics, 1962-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Lyons - Government Regulation of Labor Relations on Railroads since 1920, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Shopmen's Strike, 1922-1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Material not Usable, 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Bibliography, 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Reynolds and Killingsworth - Entries on Labor and Politics (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Bibliographies, 1975-1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Gus Tyler - Bibliography, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Influence of Canadian Law, 1917-1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- The People's News Service, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- MacKay, The Progressive Movement, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  Excerpt from Kenneth MacKay's The Progressive Movement of 1924
- Committee of 48, 1921 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Non-Partisan League, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- People's Legislative Service, 1921-1928 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Henry David - Labor and Political Action After World War I, 1919-1924, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- UMW Executive Board Minutes, 1906-1930 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- UMW - Harding, 1920-1923 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- AFL - 1920 (May 13 - July 28) (Box 27, Folder 20)
- AFL - 1920 (July 30 - September 29) (Box 27, Folder 21)
- AFL - 1920 (September 30)-1921 (March 2), 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- AFL - 1922 (January 13-February 21), 1922-1933 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- AFL - 1921 (March 4-May 26) (Box 27, Folder 24)
- AFL - 1921 (July 12-December 28) (Box 27, Folder 25)
- AFL - 1922 (February 27-April 3) (Box 27, Folder 26)
- AFL - 1922 (April 4-July 25) (Box 27, Folder 27)
- AFL - 1922 (August 1-28) (Box 27, Folder 28)
- AFL - 1922 (August 31-September 30) (Box 27, Folder 29)
- AFL - 1922 (October 4-November 2) (Box 27, Folder 30)
- AFL - 1922 (November 2-December 18) (Box 27, Folder 31)
- AFL 1922, 1921-1922 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- AFL 1922 continued (Box 27, Folder 33)
- AFL 1922 - Part 3 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- AFL 1922 - Part 4 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- AFL 1922 - Part 5 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- AFL 1922 - Part 6 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- AFL 1922 - Part 7 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- AFL - 1923 (December 30, 1922-January 17, 1923), 1922-1923 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Hoover (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Hoover and Labor (Box 28, Folder 2)
- La Follette (Box 28, Folder 3)
- La Follette, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- La Follette, Early, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- La Follette, General-1924 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Death of La Follette (Box 28, Folder 7)
- McAdoo 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Everett Sanders (Coolidge sec.) (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Richberg Bio Data (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Vardaman (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Wheeler (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Wheeler (Box 28, Folder 13)
- R. Progressives and Early 1920's (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Keating Papers of no Value to Me (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Overviews, 1920-22, re RLB, 1920-1922 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Constitutions Re Politics, BLF+E, etc. (Box 28, Folder 17)
- H's Campaign Speeches 1920 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- NAM 1920, 1921, 1922+ 1923, 1920-1923 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Railroad labor and Politics 1920 AFL (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Railroad Labor and Politics 1920 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Railroad Labor and Politics 1920 AFL (Box 28, Folder 22)
- 1920 Election (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Labor and Politics 1920 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Election of 1920 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Politics 1920 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Labour+Politics 1920 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Labor and Politics 1920- Each #1 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Labor and Politics 1920-Esch #2 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Labor and Politics 1920-Esch #3 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Labor and Politics 1920 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- 1920 Election (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Overviews (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Overviews (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Plumb or EC- 1 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Plumb or EC- 2 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Introd. (Box 28, Folder 37)
- AFL Summary of RA (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Introd. (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Intro. (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Introd. (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Introduction- 1 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- W.B. Wilson Papers, His later recollection of relations with Pres. Wilson (Box 28, Folder 43)
- 1916 Election (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Introduction (Box 28, Folder 45)
- 1916 Presidential Vote (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Wages and Strikes July- Sept.1919 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Introduction (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Introduction- 2 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Introduction- 3 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- Plumb Plan Revision (Box 28, Folder 51)
- PP (1919) Revision (Box 28, Folder 52)
- PP Material of no value (Box 28, Folder 53)
- PP Material believed of value (Box 28, Folder 54)
- PPL Finances (Box 28, Folder 55)
- Press and PP (Box 28, Folder 56)
- Criticism of PP in 1919 (Box 28, Folder 57)
- Other Views re PP (Box 28, Folder 58)
- 1922 Election (Box 28, Folder 59)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive- Firemen and Enginemen 1922 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 61)
- CPPA Proc.-Nat'l Dec. 1922 Conf. (Box 28, Folder 62)
- 1922 Congressional Elections (Box 28, Folder 63)
- Pratt, Morris Hillguit (Box 28, Folder 64)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen 1922 (Box 28, Folder 65)
- The Story of Labor (Box 28, Folder 66)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 5)
- NP League in N Dakota (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Lilienthal (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Notes for Amending "Howell- Barbley: Round One" (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Carrier Opposition to Howell- Barbley: Round One (Box 29, Folder 9)
- CPPA 1924-25, 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- CPPA 1924-25 (2), 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- L-W Campaign (Box 29, Folder 12)
- La Follette Campaign (Box 29, Folder 13)
- 1924 Political Campaign (1) (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 15)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 16)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 17)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 18)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 19)
- 1924 (6) (Box 29, Folder 20)
- 1924 (7) (Box 29, Folder 21)
- 1924 Political Campaign (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Rr. Labor and LaF.- Wheeler Campaign (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Rr. Labor and La F.- Wheeler Campaign (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Rr. Labor and La F.- Wheeler Campaign (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Barkley Papers (Box 29, Folder 26)